that. Er there was we were we arrived
there, we were detained and then we were
Yes.
And when these dehumanized torture victims
returned home it looked like this.
Because words stand against words concerning it
possible humiliation tortures like these
jubilant activists claim to have
subjected to, each one simply gets
decide for yourself what appears reasonable.
What we do know, however, is that Tunberg did not
as when Sveriges Television wanted to do
Minister of Civil Defense Carl Oscar Bolin
responsible for the pro-Palestinian mob
who persecuted him in reference to
that the government might not have been